let questions = [
    {   // QUESTION #1
        question: "Which of the following was NOT taxed in the stamp act? ",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "Dice and playing cards",
        choiceB: "Gunpowder",
        choiceC: "Legal documents ",
        choiceD: "Newspapers",
        correct: "B"
    }, { // QUESTION #2
        question: "Who was the British Prime Minister during the time of the Stamp Act?",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "Lord North",
        choiceB: "Tony Blair",
        choiceC: "William Pitt",
        choiceD: "Lord Sterling",
        correct: "C"
    },
    {   // QUESTION #3
        question: "What year did the Boston Massacre take place?",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "1770",
        choiceB: "1776",
        choiceC: "1777",
        choiceD: "1812",
        correct: "A"
    }, { // QUESTION #4
        question: "Who was in charge of all British forces in North America during the start of the American Revolution? ",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "Charles Cornwallis",
        choiceB: "Henry Clinton",
        choiceC: "Thomas Gage",
        choiceD: "John Burgoyne",
        correct: "C"
    }, { // QUESTION #5
        question: "In 1774, the first Continental Congress was held in this city:",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "Boston",
        choiceB: "New York",
        choiceC: "Chicago",
        choiceD: "Philadelphia",
        correct: "D"
    }, { // QUESTION #6
        question: "At the first Continental Congress, every colony sent delegates except for : ",
        imgSrc: " ",
        choiceA: "South Carolina",
        choiceB: "Virginia",
        choiceC: "Georgia",
        choiceD: "New York",
        correct: "C"
    }, { // QUESTION #7
        question: "When did the "battles" of Lexington and Concord take place? ",
        imgSrc: " ",
        choiceA: "December 24, 1776",
        choiceB: "May 19, 1775",
        choiceC: "April 19, 1776",
        choiceD: "April 19, 1775",
        correct: "D"
    }, { // QUESTION #8
        question: "Who was the British Prime Minister by the time of Lexington and Concord?",
        imgSrc: " ",
        choiceA: "Lord North",
        choiceB: "Lord Sterling",
        choiceC: "Lord Waxford",
        choiceD: "George III",
        correct: "A"
    }, { // QUESTION #9
        question: "During Paul Revere's famous ride to warn of the British coming, he was caught. Who actually made it to Concord? ",
        imgSrc: "",
        choiceA: "William Dawes",
        choiceB: "Samuel Prescott",
        choiceC: "John Hancock",
        choiceD: "Samuel Adams",
        correct: "B"
    }, { // QUESTION #10
        question: "Who's quote is this? 'The die is now cast. The Colonies must either submit or triumph' ",
        imgSrc: " ",
        choiceA: "Benjamin Franklin",
        choiceB: "George Washington",
        choiceC: "John Adams",
        choiceD: "George III",
        correct: "D"
    }
];